schoolexplore.com 2006-04-12

# 

**Information Collected by Occasio Group**

**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information**

Occasio Group collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the Occasio Group site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site. 

Occasio Group may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information. 

**How Collected Information is Used**

The non-personally identifiable information that Occasio Group collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. 

If you elect to provide Occasio Group with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from Occasio Group and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other Occasio Group sales and marketing efforts. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by Occasio Group. There are instances, however, in which your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. 

Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of Occasio Group on an anonymous basis. 

When you request information from Occasio Group or any university affiliated on the website, we may transfer that information within Occasio Group or route your information to university, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, so that they may provide the information on the program that you requested. 

We may also disclose information to a third party who provides substantially similar services as the original service about which you requested more information. In such situations, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that Occasio Group is very careful in selecting companies with whom it does business. 

In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that Occasio Group, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information. 

Finally, Occasio Group may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials. 

**Security**

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within Occasio Group or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while Occasio Group will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. 

**Choice**

**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out**

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting Occasio Group web sites. 

**Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Opting-Out**

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to Occasio Group. If you choose to provide such information to Occasio Group, you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. 

**Access/Accuracy**

To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, Occasio Group wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Occasio Group should you need to update or correct that information. 

**Children's Privacy**

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Occasio Group is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

**Commitment**

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Occasio Group's web sites are constantly changing to meet these demands. 

While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention. 

**Your Consent**

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Occasio Group's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. 

**Contacting Us**

    For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding Occasio Group's Privacy Policy, you may email us at 

    Privacy
    
    Occasio Group 

    13553 Poway Rd

    Suite #630

    Poway, CA 92064-9877

    US

Thank you for visiting our web site. We hope you have a pleasant experience while you are here.
